let MCQS = [{
    question: "Most of the series had our heroes preoccupied with retrieving which items?",
    choice1: "Pym Particles",
    choice2: "Midi-chlorinates",
    choice3: "Deathly Hollows",
    choice4: "Infinity Stones",
    answer: 3
},
    {
        question: "The MCU heroes treat this guy as their boss. What's his name?",
        choice1: "Nick Fury",
        choice2: "Phil Coulson",
        choice3: "Howard Stark",
        choice4: "Peter Parker",
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "This rare element took center stage in Black Panther. Can you name it?",
        choice1: "Vibranium",
        choice2: "Plutonium",
        choice3: "Uranium",
        choice4: "Adamantium",
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "When not in hero duty, Hawkeye goes by which name?",
        choice1: "Johann Schmidt",
        choice2: "Tony Stark",
        choice3: "Clint Barton",
        choice4: "Stan Lee",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Gamora's sister?",
        choice1: "Black Widow",
        choice2: "Mantis",
        choice3: "Nebula",
        choice4: "Aurora",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is Black Widow's given name?",
        choice1: "Wanda Maximoff",
        choice2: "Natasha Romanoff",
        choice3: "Mary Jane",
        choice4: "Gwen Stacy",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Doctor Strange practiced which medical specialty?",
        choice1: "Psychiatry",
        choice2: "Cardiology",
        choice3: "Dentistry",
        choice4: "Neurosurgery",
        answer: 3
    },{
        question: "What can Thanos do with all the Infinity Stones?",
        choice1: "The Crackle",
        choice2: "The Twist",
        choice3: "The Snap",
        choice4: "The Pop",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Who is considered to be the First Avenger?",
        choice1: "Spider-Man",
        choice2: "Iron Man",
        choice3: "Captain Marvel",
        choice4: "Captain America",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What country was Wanda Maximoff from?",
        choice1: "Estonia",
        choice2: "Sokovia",
        choice3: "Latvia",
        choice4: "Russia",
        answer: 1
    }];